A Guide to the Institute of International Education records, Alumni and Historical Files, RG 1 FA1289
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Historical Files, 3
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Annual Meeting - January 18, 1965 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 40), Reel 35, Index 40 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - April 19, 1965 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 41), Reel 35, Index 41 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - October 18, 1965 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 42), Reel 35, Index 42 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Annual Meeting - January 17, 1966 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 43), Reel 35, Index 43 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - April 18, 1966 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 44), Reel 35, Index 44 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - October 17, 1966 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 45), Reel 35, Index 45 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Annual Meeting - January 16, 1967 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 46), Reel 35, Index 46 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - April 17, 1967 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 47), Reel 35, Index 47 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - October 16, 1967 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 48), Reel 35, Index 48 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Annual Meeting - January 15, 1968 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 48), Reel 35, Index 48 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - April 22, 1968 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 49), Reel 35, Index 49 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - October 21, 1968 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 50), Reel 35, Index 50 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Annual Meeting - February 19, 1969 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 51), Reel 35, Index 51 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - April 21, 1969 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 52), Reel 35, Index 52 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - October 20, 1969 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 53), Reel 35, Index 53 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Annual Meeting - January 19, 1970 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 54), Reel 35, Index 54 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - April 15, 1970 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 55), Reel 35, Index 55 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - October 19, 1970 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 56), Reel 35, Index 56 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Annual Meeting - January 17, 1971 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 57), Reel 35, Index 57 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - April 19, 1971 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 58), Reel 35, Index 58 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - October 18, 1971 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 59), Reel 35, Index 59 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Annual Meeting - January 17, 1972 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 60), Reel 35, Index 60 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting: April 17, 1972 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 61), Reel 35, Index 61 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - October 16, 1972 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 62), Reel 35, Index 62 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Annual Meeting - January 23, 1973 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 63), Reel 35, Index 63 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Joint Meeting - Board of Trustees and National Council - April 23, 1973 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 64), Reel 35, Index 64 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - October 15, 1973 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 65), Reel 35, Index 65 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Annual Meeting - January 22, 1974 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 66), Reel 35, Index 66 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Joint Meeting of the Board of Trustees and National Council - April 22, 1974 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 67), Reel 35, Index 67 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - October 21, 1974 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 35, Index 68), Reel 35, Index 68 (Reel 35)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - January 21, 1975 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 69), Reel 36, Index 69 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Joint Meeting of the Board of Trustees and National Council - April 21, 1975 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 70), Reel 36, Index 70 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - October 20, 1975 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 71), Reel 36, Index 71 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Annual Meeting - January 27, 1976 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 72), Reel 36, Index 72 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Joint Meeting of the Board of Trustees and National Council - April 19, 1976 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 73), Reel 36, Index 73 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - October 18, 1976 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 74), Reel 36, Index 74 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Annual Meeting: January 28, 1977 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 74), Reel 36, Index 74 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Board of Trustees- National Council Meeting - April 18, 1977 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 75), Reel 36, Index 75 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - October 17, 1977 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 76), Reel 36, Index 76 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - January 23, 1978 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 77), Reel 36, Index 77 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Joint Board of Trustees and IIE Council Meeting - April 17, 1978 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 78), Reel 36, Index 78 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting - October 16, 1978 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 79), Reel 36, Index 79 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees Meeting - January 22, 1979 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 80), Reel 36, Index 80 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Joint Board of Trustees and IIE Council Meeting - April 16, 1979 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 81), Reel 36, Index 81 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Board of Trustees Meeting - October 15, 1979 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 82), Reel 36, Index 82 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Board of Trustees Meeting - January 28, 1980 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 83), Reel 36, Index 83 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Regular Meeting: April 21, 1980 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 84), Reel 36, Index 84 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Board of Trustees Meeting - October 20, 1980 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 85), Reel 36, Index 85 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - IIE Board of Trustees Meeting - January 30, 1981 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 86), Reel 36, Index 86 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Joint Meeting: Board of Trustees and Council - April 28, 1981 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 87), Reel 36, Index 87 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Board of Trustees Meeting - October 19, 1981 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 88), Reel 36, Index 88 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Board of Trustees Meeting - January 29, 1982 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 89), Reel 36, Index 89 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Board of Trustees Meeting - May 3, 1982 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 90), Reel 36, Index 90 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Board of Trustees Meeting - October 18, 1982 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 91), Reel 36, Index 91 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Board of Trustees Meeting - January 28, 1983 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 92), Reel 36, Index 92 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Board of Trustees Meeting - April 18, 1983 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 93), Reel 36, Index 93 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Board of Trustees Meeting - October 17, 1983 - Agenda and Documentation (Reel 36, Index 94), Reel 36, Index 94 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Special meeting - 4-10-46 - Agenda (Reel 36, Index 95), Reel 36, Index 95 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees Meeting - May 9, 1946 - Agenda (Reel 36, Index 96), Reel 36, Index 96 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees Meeting - October 24, 1946 - Agenda (Reel 36, Index 97), Reel 36, Index 97 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Special meeting - June 25, 1947 - Agenda (Reel 36, Index 98), Reel 36, Index 98 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Annual Meeting - October 23, 1947 - Agenda (Reel 36, Index 99), Reel 36, Index 99 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Special meeting - March 29, 1948 - Agenda (Reel 36, Index 100), Reel 36, Index 100 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Special meeting - June 29, 1948 - Agenda (Reel 36, Index 101), Reel 36, Index 101 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Annual Meeting - November 15, 1948 - Agenda (Reel 36, Index 102), Reel 36, Index 102 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Adjourned Meeting - February 21, 1949 - Agenda (Reel 36, Index 103), Reel 36, Index 103 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees Meeting - May 16, 1949 - Agenda (Reel 36, Index 104), Reel 36, Index 104 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Annual Meeting November 14, 1949 - Agenda (Reel 36, Index 105), Reel 36, Index 105 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees Meeting - February 13, 1950 - Agenda (Reel 36, Index 106), Reel 36, Index 106 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees Meeting - May 15, 1950 - Agenda (Reel 36, Index 107), Reel 36, Index 107 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees Meeting - November 30, 1950 - Agenda (Reel 36, Index 108), Reel 36, Index 108 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees Meeting - February 12-26, 1951 - Agenda (Reel 36, Index 109), Reel 36, Index 109 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees Meeting - May 14, 1951 - Agenda (Reel 36, Index 110), Reel 36, Index 110 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees - Special meeting - September 21, 1951 - Agenda (Reel 36, Index 112), Reel 36, Index 112 (Reel 36)
  - IIE Board of Trustees Meeting - November 12, 1951 - Agenda (Reel 36, Index 113), Reel 36, Index 113 (Reel 36)